https://mermade.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Mermade Inc., respects the privacy of its website visitors and adheres to best practices, applicable U.S. federal laws, and acknowledges the European Union General Data Protection Regulation implementation.
Mermade, Inc., our website address is: https://mermade.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Contact forms
We collect the data provided by you. We store that information for marketing purposes, we do not share that information.
Cookies
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We do not share information outside of our company, except with other North American Filtration Companies and we use it for marketing purposes.
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
For GDPR requests please contact Stacey Painter at: spainter@Chemtrac.com
Additional information
Third parties
This site may be using third-party cloud storage to store backups of its audit logs where personal information is collected.
Additional data
This site creates and stores an activity log that capture the IP address, username, email address and tracks user activity (like when a user makes a purchase). Information will be stored locally for 30 days and remotely for 1 year. Information on remote logs cannot be cleared for security purposes.
Call Us
TEL: (803) 793-4265FAX: (803) 793-4332
Links
HOMEABOUTPRODUCTSCONTACT
Meet Us
MER-MADE FILTER, INC.11746 Charleston-Augusta RoadP.O. Box 306Denmark, SC 29042sales@mermade.com
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
X
